confirm our plan design in Phase 3, and also confirm that the 10-milligram dose is the right dose to take forward.
I think at this point, we're still in discussions with our partner company on the right approach with PTC,
on the right approach with any further engagement with FDA. And I think as soon as we have clarity on that,
we'll, of course, and have those discussions with FDA. We can keep the markets updated, but I think no further
comment until those discussions are complete.
Next question.
Thank you. Your next question comes from the line of Graham Parry from Citigroup. Please go ahead.
Okay, thanks for taking my follow-up. Just on Cozentix, actually, it would be useful if you could qualify the
growth to net adjustments, both in the base year and this year at the quarter. And previously, you talked about
US growing mid-single-digit growth over the mid-term to an 8 billion peak on that asset that was absent from the
release and side stage. I just wonder if that still stands. Thank you.
Yes.
So, on the growth to nets and adjustments for Cozentix from quarter one last year?
Yeah. So, I think if we exclude the growth to net impact on Cozentix, Cozentix moves into a positive growth territory for the US.
I think to be exact, around 1%, 0% to 1%, closer to 1% for the quarter. We have to think of, and then I think if we think of an overall basis,
we have two.
So, if we take a look at our two percentage points in our base for growth to net in the US in Q1 2025, I think we also have a positive impact this year.
The net comes to about 1% on our overall fee amount.
And I think, you know, Graham, when you look going forward, yeah, we continue to expect to be in this mid-single-digit range globally.
And I think that will be a mix of US and ex-US.
And we're going to have to, I think, see how the coming quarters evolve.
But that's our current expectation is that we would be in that mid-single-digit range.
Clearly, the peak sales for Cozentix would most likely be in 2027, given the IRA event in 2028 would impact the overall pricing in Medicare, but also into the Medicaid best price in 2028.
So, all of those dynamics are unfolding alongside the PMR launch.